Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. Heat. N.
Heat up
here.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Okay.
And then I'm going to turn off the other
one and turn on A1 now.
two one
>> and they're live
in the chat where you're viewing and
this is your very first time.
I have no sound on YouTube.
>> There's no audio. There's no audio on
online.
>> Hang on.
>> How about now?
I'm seeing a stream audio.
>> Is there audio red?
>> Yeah, I have them red.
>> No, you have the lapels red. All
>> right. So, let's uh
>> put a one in the chat if you can hear us
now. Any
volume?
Testing. One, two, three. Testing. Can
you hear us? You can hear but very low.
You hear the production team?
>> All right.
>> All right. Well,
>> I can't hear you.
>> Okay. There we go.
>> Okay. Okay, you guys hear us now?
>> Looks like
>> All right. Okay.
>> Well, I only said welcome uh to to
Living Man Church. It's good to see you
guys. So, now you can can hear us.
That's wonderful. Uh we're just so happy
to worship with you here on the Sabbath.
Please, we this is an international
church. We have viewers all around the
world. We want to know where you're
viewing from. And we also want to know
if this is your very first time. And if
you could put your name in the chat,
that would uh be great because sometimes
your handles don't match the name. And
it looks like I have no sound.
>> It looks like you have no sound. So you
guys can hear me. Is that right?
>> Yeah.
>> Just put a chat.
>> They're just saying me. So it sounds
like Atanti, you might want to check if
your mic is on.
>> Yeah, mic is on.
>> Mic is on.
>> Okay.
Well, um
>> Okay. Yeah,
>> they're hearing me through you. So,
you're going to have to carry the
welcome because I have no mic.
>> All right. Well, we want to welcome I'm
going to be you today. We want to
welcome all of you
>> who are watching from um around the
world. We're looking at where you are u
where you're viewing from and um we're
excited to have you guys with us. And I
saw that you guys were actually enjoying
the
>> you guys can hear me now.
>> Yeah, they can hear now.
>> Do you hear me from me or do you hear me
through his mic? Do you hear me clearly?
>> Yeah, they hear you good.
>> Okay.
>> And we did see that you guys were
enjoying the uh the trivia at the at the
uh opening of the
>> of the program. So, um praise God.
Praise God. Yeah. We're not sure why
we're having this this uh audio
>> Well, let's pause
>> difficulty, but
>> Okay, let's both of us talk, right? I'm
talking.
>> Mhm. And I'm talking.
>> Okay. So, can you hear us both clearly?
>> Sounds much better.
>> Better. Great. Okay. Well, good. Well,
all I said both times was welcome. We're
happy you're here. So, for the third
time, welcome. and we're happy that you
are here worshiping with us today. Uh
this is the Sabbath and we have viewing
audience from all around the world here
to worship on this Sabbath day and we
are thankful some of you I did some of
you kind of know the role so you knew
what I was saying. Um but you were from
Bermuda and uh that's the only one that
I can u see right now that so welcome
from Bermuda. I saw that and I'd have to
scroll up. So, please continue to put in
the chat where you're viewing from and
if this is your very first time. Just
again want to say a very special welcome
to all of you here to Living Mana
Church.
>> Yes. And uh we do have a couple of uh we
have something exciting happening today.
We have someone that is going to be
joining us um by profession of faith. Um
and uh so we're looking forward to that.
And I think we have a second uh reading
for a transfer. Yeah, we have transfer
two transfers and transfers out.
>> Actually, we have two for that that are
a family that's out and then they're
both they're both out the second
reading.
>> Yeah.
>> Um and then but we do have a profession
of faith. So I missed some here. San
Andreas Island. I think that was a one.
So welcome to Living Manage Church. We
have Angquilla, Canada, Trinidad,
Washington State. Robert, welcome. Good
to see you here. Good to see all of you
here. Just want to welcome you to Living
Mana Church. I think it's Columbus,
Ohio. Welcome to Living Mana Church. If
I missed some, I apologize.
We have Georgia, Ken and Sam from
Chrisfield, Maryland. Welcome to Living
Mana Church. We have I think Evelyn from
St. Croy.
All right. And they are have some people
are saying my volume is very low. So
again, put a one if my in the chat if if
if you agree that my volume is very low.
>> Got to welcome Jamaica. You can
>> you might you might just need to talk
and y'all could just turn this way so
you could be more on my mic when we
talk.
>> Oh yes. Okay. Well, I think that helps.
>> It probably that's not going to be good.
Yeah.
>> But anyway, we do want to welcome all of
you where you're viewing from. Um and uh
just thank you for joining us today. Uh,
and again, we have today a very special
Sabbath school goal. We haven't done
this before.
>> Okay, we're getting one. So, ones that
you hear me. I did say save one if you
hear me well. Right. Good.
>> I just don't even remember now.
>> Okay. It's not low. I'm going I'm going
with Takara. I'm going I'm rolling with
that.
>> Yes. We're just sticking with that. So,
whatever happens.
>> Welcome from H Spanish Wells, Bahamas.
Welcome to Living Manage Church. I was I
was just saying um that
uh we are going to be um looking today
for Sabbath school. We're going to be
looking at the photo theology Bible
study software.
>> Yes.
>> And we're super excited about that. Um
>> you can call it an app, but I
>> Yeah,
>> but it's Yes, we're excited about that.
>> Yeah. And we got guests coming on, so
we're going to kind of take a little
tour through the palace. M
>> uh and that's what we're going to be
talking about today. So again, I'm super
excited. We have guests that are going
to be joining us that have been using
this software. Um and um we're just
going to talk about I think the
importance of you know having a
membership that is wellstudied in the
word of God.
>> Yes. So that's going to kind of be our
theme as we get into the
>> importance of you individually studying
the Bible for yourself and having this
app is to help you the suite the app
whatever you want to call it this tech
um it is to help you to be able to do
that. Um because you know some of my
first memories of you
and definitely in our first early years
of marriage and I've said this on here
before is he was carrying around people
be like why do you have all that Bible
knowledge Pastor Meyers? My early
memories of Pastor Meyers are the big
strong concordance. It's a big book. So
it was almost like
>> like it's like you had to carry that
thing around is wild. But you would
carry he would carry it around like it
was always like right there and his
Bible
>> and a notepad and a pen.
>> Mhm.
>> And then you got into computer and then
quickly you you you switched over to
computer like you know keeping your
notes and stuff like that. But um he was
always studying but that those were his
tools. Those were the tools that he used
to study. Um, and this suite and app is,
and we'll get more into this, but this
is going to be
uh by God's grace like your Strong's
concordance and Bible, but much much
much much
I don't want to say, well, I will say
deeper in the sense that it it's it's
>> it's fun. It's interactive. You're going
to be learning so much and being trained
in so many different ways. And it's made
so that so many different personality
types because everybody learns a little
bit different and wants things a little
bit different. So it's going to help
match so many different varieties of
different learning styles and people's
personal preference.
>> Yeah.
>> Which is great. I mean that was the old
old school way
>> to do it
>> 27 30 years ago. That was
>> very very tedious.
>> Very tedious.
>> You had to go down the line of how many
times is this word mentioned?
all the way. Yeah.
>> With technology, we don't have to do
that anymore, but we can get
>> that knowledge
>> and a lot more.
>> Yeah.
>> Like imagine you would have had this 30
years ago.
>> Yeah.
>> So, uh we will talk more about the app
um and answer all these questions
because like blessing Joy wants to know
is it used um on an iPad or just a PC
only. So, we'll get into that. But we
have
>> memberships that transfers and then we
have a profession of faith. So,
Um, let's see.
>> And then we'll pray before we actually
begin our uh our uh Sabbath school
study. So,
>> of course,
>> uh prayer is coming up is happening.
We're going to do these transfers first.
Yeah.
>> Yes. So, we have a second reading. And I
have to make a correction because last
week we did do a first reading. The part
that was incorrect was the uh for
Michael Britt was he was coming in. and
he's actually going out to McDonald Road
7th Day Adventist Church. And so this
will be a second reading for him with
that little um amendment I guess to it.
Um so Michael Britt second reading going
to McDonald 7th Day Adventist Church in
McDonald, Tennessee. And then Darius
Lynn Darius and Lynn Ziggler. This is
their second reading and they are going
from LMLC to Tri City 7th Day Adventist
Church in Prattville, Alabama. So, um
those are two second readings for
Michael Britt and Darius and Lynn
Ziggler. And again, Michael Britt is
going to the McDonald Road 7th Day
Adventist Church and the Zigglers are
going to Tri City 7th Day Adventist
Church.
>> Okay. So, second readings for both.
>> Both. Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> So, we're going to go ahead and
entertain a motion. um to uh accept
their transfers out. So, uh if anyone
one of our members would like to go
ahead and um make a motion
and then we'll uh look for a second,
then we'll go ahead and uh and vote. So,
um
and and yes, uh while waiting for that
motion, yes, brother Jason, the the old
way. He said the OG way.
>> Yeah. Was indeed very effective. Uh and
uh we don't hate on it at all.
>> Yeah. We're not hating on it. It's just
we're in we're
>> we have to pro we have we have to
progress with times and the way people
are choosing to want to learn and
everybody has an app on their phone or
>> Yeah.
>> Um so yes, definitely.
>> So we got a Okay, so we got the we've
got a motion. Uh we've got a second.
Let's go ahead and vote. All in favor uh
put a one in the chat and um
>> we will have miss you officially on the
books.
>> Yeah.
>> But we know that you'll be visiting
Living Man Church and we're here for you
always.
>> Amen.
>> This is my one.
>> All right. So
uh
we know there is a little delay so these
ones will start coming in.
>> Yes. Um,
all right.
There we go.
And it's uh
Okay, there we go. The ones are coming
in.
>> Yep, the ones are coming in.
>> Well, thank you.
>> So, yeah. Uh, we're going to go ahead
and um
that motion has been passed. So guys, we
will definitely uh miss your name on the
books, but uh as we've said, we know
that um you are uh you know, still what
we call a faith member.
>> Yes. A part of the LMLC church family.
>> So all right. Well, amen. Praise God.
And then we have a uh
>> a profession of faith of faith.
>> Yes. So right before we do that,
>> you know what?
Okay. t-shirt message or this.
>> Let's do this.
>> Okay, let's since we're already our
mind's already here. All right, we're
going to bring on
>> Jacob.
>> Um,
>> let's go ahead and They're trying to
find out where you get your shirts from,
Tante. But in the meantime,
>> Jacob, uh, welcome, sir.
>> Just to answer that question really
quick forget, honestly, I get them off
of Amazon.
That's the truth. All right.
>> There you go. Jacob, welcome, man. How
are you?
>> Hi, Jacob. Welcome.
>> Doing great. Yeah. Thank you very much
for having me here.
>> Absolutely, man. Absolutely. Um,
>> we are excited.
>> We're excited to have you on. And, uh,
just so that the audience knows, not
only will we be doing a profession of
faith for Jacob, but Jacob's going to be
staying on with us because we're going
to be he's one of the ones that's been
using the photo theology Bible software.
So, he will be one of our guests and
we're super excited about that. Yes.
>> Um,
>> so, Jacob, please introduce yourself to
our audience. Let us know a little bit.
Let them know more about you if you
don't mind.
>> Yeah. So, so, uh, yeah, Jacob Goodwin. I
live in Paradise, California, and about
45 years old. Uh, and I actually, uh,
first was introduced to Pastor Myers. It
was a uh youth convention going on down
in San Jose area like early 2000s or
something like that. But uh but anyway,
so uh today's just kind of like a u a
promise being fulfilled by the Lord as
far as getting me to a point where I am
today as far as just ready to uh just
receive instruction and and just be
developed into the man God's called me
to be. So I'm really thankful to be
here.
>> Amen.
>> Amen. Amen. So, where are you? Where are
you? Where where are you from?
>> Okay. Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> Paradise, California. Yes. Okay. Well,
we are happy for you to uh become a
member, an official member of Living
Mana Church and you are joining by
profession of faith. And for some of you
who are wondering uh what that is, this
profession of faith is like you're
already a Christian and you don't feel
like you need to be rebaptized
um and you uh want to be an official
member of the the Seventh Day Adventist
Church. And so uh that is what is what
is happening today. And then uh the
other way is to actually be baptized to
become a member or to transfer your
membership. So those are the ways to
become a member of Living Man Church.
>> Yeah. So, we're going to go ahead and um
Jacob, we're going to read through these
uh baptismal vows. And again, this is um
I know that you have been um
uh your story is a little bit different
in terms of you're not just becoming an
Adventist,
>> right? Um but um at any rate, we're
going to go ahead and read through these
vows and if you just respond in the
affirmative and then we'll make a motion
to accept you into fellowship of the
Living Man online church and uh we'll
vote that and by God's grace welcome you
in today.
>> So um do you believe in God the Father,
the Son, uh his son Jesus Christ and in
the Holy Spirit?
>> Yes, absolutely. Do you accept the death
of Jesus Christ on Calvary as the
atoning sacrifice for your sins and
believe that through faith in his shed
blood you are saved from sin and its
penalty?
>> Yes.
>> Do you renounce the world in his sinful
ways and having accepted Jesus Christ as
your personal savior believe that God
for Christ's sake has forgiven you and
given you a new heart?
>> Yes. Do you accept uh by faith the
righteousness of Christ, recognizing him
as your intercessor in the heavenly
sanctuary, and claim his promise to
strengthen to strengthen you by his
inddwelling spirit so that you may
receive power to do his will?
>> Yes.
>> All right. Do you believe that God's
Bible that the Bible is God's inspired
word and that it constitutes the only
rule of faith and practice for the
Christian?
>> Yes. Do you accept the ten commandments
as still binding upon Christians? And
and is it your purpose by the power of
the indwelling Christ to keep this law
according to the four including the
fourth commandment which requires the
observance of the seventh day of the
week as the Sabbath of the Lord?
>> Yes.
>> Amen. Uh do you look forward to the soon
coming of Jesus as the blessed hope in
your heart and are you determined and uh
to be ready to meet the Lord and to do
all in your power to witness to his
salvation?
um by life and word and to help others
to be ready for his glorious appearing.
>> Yes.
>> Do you do you accept the teaching of
biblical gifts and believe that the gift
of prophecy is one of the identifying
marks of the remnant church?
>> Yes.
>> Amen. Do you believe in church
organization? And is it your purpose to
support the church by your tithes and
offerings
uh and personal effort and influence?
>> Yes.
Um, and do you believe that your body is
a temple of the Holy Spirit and that you
will honor it according to the word of
God?
>> Yes.
>> And um,
finally, well, not finally, we got one
or two more. I know and Do you know and
understand the fundamental Bible
principles as taught by the Seventh Day
Adventist Church? And is it your purpose
by the grace of God to order your life
in harmony with these principles?
>> Yes.
And uh finally, do you accept the
Seventh Day Adventist Church is the
remnant church of Bible prophecy and
that people of every nation, race, and
language are invited and accepted into
its fellowship?
>> Yes.
>> And do you desire to be a member in this
local congregation of the World Church?
>> Yes, I do.
>> Amen. Amen. So, we're going to go ahead,
guys, and uh open the floor for a
motion.
um and a second and then we will go
ahead and vote by putting a seven in the
chat. So once we get our motion, we've
got a motion. Um do we have a second?
We've got we've got yay coming in.
>> Yay.
>> All right. So, we'll call that the
second
>> and then we're going to go ahead and
vote. The sevens are already coming. So,
>> seven in the chat and um Jacob, we want
to welcome you.
>> We are so happy to have you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Um
>> thank you. Yeah.
>> Amen. We're excited to to receive you
into the Fellowship of Living Mana and
uh we trust that God is going to use
you. you know, this church, we're not a
church that we don't just sit down in
the pews because we don't have any pews.
Um, so we can't just sit in the pews.
>> We don't just we just don't watch the
screens either,
>> right? So,
>> we don't have we don't want just screen
watchers, viewers either.
>> Yep. Um, so we definitely want to
welcome you and, you know, however the
Lord will lead you to um to minister on
his behalf, whether it's local, whether
it's online. Um we just uh pray that you
know you will find your your uh your way
uh to be able to share the this truth
with those who you come in contact with.
So
>> yes, everyone continue to welcome Jacob
as many people are welcoming you in the
chat. Uh the Living Mana Church family
is happy to officially have you as a
member of Living Mana online church. And
uh we should pray over Jacob, but we
know Jacob, you're not going anywhere.
you're going to be here with us during
Sabbath school as we go through um uh
this photo theology app.
>> So, let's pray. Heavenly Father, we
thank you, Lord, for Jacob um and uh his
officially being a member of Living
Mana. Lord, we pray that you would just
uh use him, Lord, in a powerful way um
to be a witness um in his uh personal
life, in his community, and Lord, even
in this online space. Lord, um just uh
bless him, Lord, and um continue to to
to guide him in the way that you would
have him to go. I pray this. We pray
this in Jesus name. Amen.
>> Amen. Amen.
>> Amen. Welcome, brother.
>> Welcome again officially.
>> Yep.
>> All right. So,
>> so um
>> message t-shirt message. God is still
writing your story. Stop trying to steal
the pen.
>> Yes. So I would say as a therapist uh
trying to steal the pen would be anxiety
and worry
>> because
we all struggle at times with just
sitting back
like God wants us and this you've
preached this many times but God wants
us to sabotage most. He wants us to
rest.
>> We have a heart and that's trust.
Resting is trusting. That's truly,
>> yeah,
>> that's what God is trying to teach us
every Sabbath. Like, take these 24 hours
and just worship me. Leave your work
alone. Leave your studies alone. Leave
all your worldly whatevers alone. And I
and just worship me and I will take I
will take care of that during that time.
That's like a time
>> now. Yeah.
>> Go ahead.
>> And I do want to let y'all know that uh
she has no idea what I'm preaching about
today.
>> No idea.
>> So, we have zero.
>> I just want to say that.
>> Okay. So, okay. But so as humans it's
hard for us to really again staff at
Tismos put down the pen and just rest.
I'm speaking for myself like I only
share things with you for I only choose
t-shirts honestly for that this each
Sabbath if it doesn't really speak to me
like I have a drawer full of these
t-shirts guys and if if it doesn't speak
to me in my current situation then I'm
like
you know
>> I'm only sharing with you what's
speaking to to me and hopefully it's
it's helping you as well but um it's
hard for us to put down the pen like we
try to
you know just do everything that we can
and you know I'm a person who wants to
like I definitely do my research try to
follow through but it's just like I
still don't it's hard for me to put down
the pen.
>> Yeah.
>> It's hard for me to just be like okay
God.
>> So right now I'm kind of like in a
situation where I have to be like
>> God what do you want? Let me just
>> put down the the pen. I've actually
taken something out of scripture like
with Gideon's story and have a fleece
and this is like my first time really
doing this. So I'm just like, okay, Lord
is when is just anyway.
>> Yeah.
>> I just, you know, I'm just I just had to
remind myself that just wait for God to
show you.
>> Yeah.
>> And that is what is difficult as a
Christian to do at times.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, sometimes on the smaller
things it's easier.
>> On the bigger things it's harder.
>> It's hard.
>> So, so yes, put down the pen.
Sabatismos. Rest in Jesus. Let him write
your story, your future, your
everything. Like you want it to be his
way and not your way because your way,
>> you're not God. You don't know the
future. So you don't know the things
that God is orchestrating in the future
that he has to like put all the things,
you know, together. So you don't want to
be off track. You want to be on God's
path for your life. Yeah.
>> So put the pen down, sabotage, and rest.
>> Yeah. Now, once again, she has no idea
what I'm preaching on, so I'm just
saying that again a second time.
>> The intro to your sermon.
>> It's the Holy Spirit intro.
>> Yep.
>> All right. Praise God.
>> All right.
>> All right. Now, the Sabbath school.
>> Yes.
>> Exciting.
>> Heavenly Father, we just ask, Lord, that
you would be with us once again as we uh
get into the Sabbath school, Lord, um
and talk about the importance of Bible
study. So, Lord, please just bless us,
bless our guests, and uh may those that
are watching, Lord, also be be blessed.
Um, we pray in Jesus name. Amen.
>> Amen. Amen.
>> All right. I am excited to Well, and
we're not bringing on our guest quite
yet. Guests, don't because but we are
bringing you on. We We want you to
share, but we're not bringing you on
quite yet because we have like a little
intro to what we're we're doing.
>> Yeah.
So um
we have I've been um
this this B this phototheology Bible
study suite or software is the result of
a whole lot of years of Bible study. And
um with this project I kind of feel like
I put everything that I could possibly
put
He's he's laughing because he did put
everything
>> and it took it's taking because I don't
think you're not done. I mean it's it's
it's usable now. It's done but you're
always he's always you know apps always
update and those type of things. So he's
always adding little things more.
>> Uh but
>> he's well I'm I don't know if you were
laughing at this. I'm laughing at what
you're saying because he put it is years
of Bible study that was already in his
head and things that he's already done.
He's poured it all into the app. Um so
it's almost like you were studying with
yourself.
>> Yeah.
>> And so when you're do when you're using
this app or um the suite, you are it's
basically like you're doing a Bible
study with Pastor Myers.
>> And the reason why I was laughing is
because
>> how much time I put
>> how much time you put into it. There's a
point where I was like, once again,
guys, here's the confession. Just like
with the beginning of this church, I was
like, well, it's a different situation,
but I was like not all in at first
because I was like, how is that going to
work? What conference would ever allow
this to happen? But anyways, four years
later, I'm so wrong. Beyond wrong. And
then with this app, I was excited about
it, the possibility of it.
But he was doing it so much, so many
hours in the day. Like like it's almost
like you turned into the app. I don't
know. was like, "Yeah, he was doing it a
lot." So, anyways, I was Yeah, but we're
But I But I say that to say
I'm So, me and this app had a lovehate
relationship because all the time you
were spending and then now that I love
the app, I've fallen in love with the
app. It's my friend now. I enjoy using
the app. Like, we used it every morning.
>> Um,
>> yeah,
>> for worship. It's a blessing. It's a
truly a true blessing and it's it's
really what I needed for my own Bible
study and for what way my brain works
like it's perfect for me and I think
it's going to be perfect for anybody who
uses it because the Bible study and the
depth and the the things that are
available on it. So let me just stop
saying that and let's
>> yeah talk. So, so we um you know when I
first started building this software, it
was basically
I was making it for my students, right?
For those people who are in my photo
theology class and who want to learn how
to use the app, I mean who want to learn
how to use the photo theology
principles. But I myself would be using
different softwares, right,
>> to do my Bible studies, to put my
sermons together and things of that
nature. And
I think at some point, like halfway
through making the app, I was like,
"Wait a minute. What would what would
take, what would it take for me to not
use any other software again?
>> What would I want this, what would I
need this app to be for me to be like,
all right, I'm using this."
>> And that's what I started building
>> like halfway through. And so when I tell
you you guys that this uh this suite, I
don't even call it an app anymore. And
let me talk about that a little bit. So
a app, you kind of get the idea that you
could use it on your phone,
>> right?
>> And you can definitely use this on your
phone, but the best way to use this is
going to be on a laptop, maybe on an
iPad, but on a screen where you could
see everything that's going on. Um,
and it is it's just been a really
powerful experience for me
>> as I'm using this this software.
So, um, what we I think what we want to
talk about. So, first of all, let me
just say this up front, right?
Um, if you are a member of Living Mana
>> on the books member like Jacob is today,
>> not a faith member.
>> We love our faith members.
>> We love our faith members, but a but an
actual living mana member on the books,
then you have uh you have access to this
app.
And the reason I'm saying it that way, I
know it is it's a Sabbath,
>> but I'm saying it that way because
because this app uses AI, there's a
there's a cost that goes with it. And
that's all I'm going to say say there,
>> but there's a cost for for me.
>> Yeah, we have made it for um
we have made it for living mana members
um to
uh to be able to access this app. Why?
because
I would like for my members to be
thoroughly equipped to have everything
that they need to be able to stand on
their own. Right? So, we're providing
this tool. We're providing this tool for
our members so that it kind of becomes
your living mana hub uh for Bible study.
So, we know we have uh we know we have
several different um
Bible, you know, several different
social media hubs. We got mighty
networks and things of that nature. But
this particular
uh platform is where Bible study is
going to take place.
>> No, John. Yes. Profession of faith. If
you're official member of this of Living
Man Church, you get it. So John was
asking profession of faith members get
it don't get it. No because I I
mentioned Jacob. John yes you are a
member and so is Jacob and you guys came
in by profession of faith and you
absolutely are official members. So you
get to um use the app and the app is for
the whole world but if you are a member
of Lev Man Church there is at no cost
for you.
>> Yes. So
>> just to be clear.
>> Right. So in this in this software
there's basically a living mana space
and uh in that living mana space it's
kind of like cut off where we have our
own little space in the app and it's a
not a little space it's a mansion space.
Mhm.
>> It's a mansion space. But in this space
uh we can um in this space we can give
me one second you guys. In this space uh
we can you know living mana members can
communicate with each other. We can um
you know do Bible study together. We can
do group studies together. And I'll show
you that in the app uh once I get my
computer just died and I need the plug
for my Mac. So that's coming to me in a
second. So just be aware of that.
>> Um but anyway, so what's happening with
this software is that members can go in,
they have group um they have uh group
you there are groups that you can study
in. Uh there's a daily devotional
and you want to talk about the
devotional or I could talk about the
devotional. We're going to bring our
guests on.
>> Yeah, we're going to bring our guests
on. I think it's well
>> there's so much in the software there's
so much
>> that um
it's hard like when I say it's like a
mansion I literally mean it's like a
>> manion.
>> So having said all that let me talk
about this.
>> We believe that it's absolutely crucial
to study the word of God to show
yourself approved.
>> Right.
>> Can I say this before you say that? And
so, um, just this week, and I hadn't
spoken to
to you about it, but I had had different
inter maybe not just this week, in the
last few weeks, just different
interactions and just realizing like
the need for personal Bible study
for
um, not just our Living Man Church
members and and viewing audience, of
course, for I think so many people. But
I think the like watching your sermons,
they love them. It's great. They share
them, they put them on social media, all
that stuff. But the need for personal
Bible study, I was just shown that that
is a huge necessity uh for so many. And
this app can assist in that um in a way
that honestly and I'm not just saying it
because you created it, but it's it's
it's
just it's just so in-depth and it's just
so easy to understand. Like literally,
it's like talking to you and studying
the Bible with you and Yeah. So that's
just what it feels like.
>> Yeah. And I will say this, the reason
why it it it is like that is because in
this in this um software, I've basically
just put the photoology principles.
>> Yes.
>> Right. And my my whole, you know,
approach to this is anyone who who has
the photoology principle principles down
is going to be able to see things in the
Bible and pull things from the Bible
that you may not have been able to see
any other way. Not that you would not
have, but you may not have been able to
see any other way.
>> And so,
>> um, this software, it doesn't study for
you,
>> right?
>> Even though it uses AI, the purpose of
this is not to study for you. The
purpose of this is to show you
>> how to study,
>> how to think for yourself, how to study
for yourself. Right.
>> Right.
>> So, um,
>> yes. What I want to do,
I want to just uh if I can share my
screen.
>> Did you want to share about the
devotions? Devotionals.
>> So, we can talk about the devotions.
>> Yeah, guys, there's so many things that
you're not going to find anywhere else.
Well, I don't think it's anywhere else,
but it's it's absolutely amazing. Um I
want to do a little backdrop for the
devotionals. Um just a little story to
make
>> them see. So um like over Christmas time
we were with a lot of our nieces and
nephews and of course he pastor was
sharing with the family just what we're
doing today about the app and you know I
don't know maybe six weeks passed and
then one of our nieces reached out to
pastor and said could you please
well I guess we well can you please um
send me one of the devotionals from the
app that are catered to me and these are
my spiritual needs. So you can go into
what she was asking you to do.
>> So I mean basically I'll just say this
way you can actually create devotionals
that you could share with other people
>> and or for yourself or with other people
and um you can tailor the devotional. So
if you know someone who's going through
a hard time with this thing, depression
or anxiety or whatever
>> or even let's just say divorce or
whatever the topic is or
>> addiction, anything.
>> You can actually uh tailor the devotion
um to
speak to that person's uh need
>> and send the devotion every day.
>> And it's personal.
>> It's personal. Like if you did it for
me, it would say it would say atante,
right? Like it's it would personally
speak to me.
>> Yeah.
>> Like literally say my name.
>> That's just one aspect, you know, that's
the devotional part, but I'm going to
share. I think our screen is up and let
me just go ahead. Now, this is so I'm
kind of this Sabbath school is kind of
like for our church members because I
want to show them here's what um you can
do with the software. for the viewing
audience too if they want to get it.
>> If you want to get it. I mean, it's open
to anybody, but we're kind of doing this
as church members. We want you to see
what we've provided for you, right? Um,
>> and if you're not official member,
>> you should want to get it just because
of the personal Bible study aspect of
it.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> So, let me I'm going to go to um and I
don't know. Can y'all see my screen real
well? It looks like it might be a little
bit. Okay,
>> so um
let me do this.
>> Uh church space. So L mana here is no
here is
the living mount of church space. my
church space right here. And as you can
see in my church space, uh we got a
whole bunch of tabs here. Okay. Um there
is uh the home tab where our
announcements are. There is the diary
tab. You can um have your own diary.
There are the groups. So you can join a
group in Bible study. Um there's the
learn section. And here for example um
in the learn let's see okay
>> zoom in a little bit. Yeah
>> on the learn tab
um you can see that we have the Sabbath
school quarterly and let me talk about
that for a second. The Sabbath school
quarterly is basically you can go into
this into this software and pull the
Sabbath school quarterly and apply the
photo theology principles to the Sabbath
school study
>> so that as you're studying that Sabbath
school it's just going to give you a
deeper level of understanding for each
lesson.
>> Okay. So that's a Sabbath school study.
Um, there is the weekly study which we
once you know everybody gets in and we
actually just uh just opened this up for
our members last week.
>> Once all of our members are in, you'll
be able to go in and see this weekly
study tab right here. So, here you'll
see the Pearl of Great Price. That's the
sermon that I preached. Was it last week
or the week before?
>> It was either last week it was the week
before
>> or the week before. But basically, it'll
take the the sermon from the past week
>> and create an entire week's study
>> so that our members can dissect that
sermon and take it to levels that I
hadn't taken it from. Right? That mean
that I hadn't uh um looked at. So
>> um
>> very very very powerful, right? Very
very very powerful. Um there's six week
cycle studies uh on the sanctuary every
article of furniture. Um you can create
your own six week uh cycle study for a
small group.
Um there is the truth series and you
could see actually the 28 fundamentals
and these are just different things. I'm
I'm not going to go through everything
right now. Here's what I one of the
things I want to show you.
>> Well, you I see Jeeves and Reginald. Who
are they?
>> So, Jeeves, we I'll talk about that in a
moment.
>> Okay.
>> Jeeves, if is um is kind of like your
your photo theology guide.
>> You can ask Jez anything about the app,
anything about any room, the principles
of the room.
>> Reginal is kind of like your tour guide
for the palace. He's going to tell you,
"Here's what this room does. Here's what
this tab is about. Um, I'm gonna show
you guys one thing real quick here.
Uh, this is Y'all get ready for this.
So, when I say that I want you as
members to be like fully equipped, I
want you to look at this defense tab.
And on this defense tab,
>> you will see,
>> wow,
>> you will see a theological combat
simulator trained to defend the faith
against real world
challengers. Watch this, guys. So, this
is this is Mr. Atheist AI.
>> You can zoom in.
>> Okay.
Um,
let me zoom out a little bit here. Okay.
So, this is Mr. Atheist AI. This is the
Muslim apologist AI.
Let me move these guys out the way here.
This is the Hebrew Israelite. This is
the Latter-day Saints. This is the
Jehovah's Witness. This is the Catholic
theologian. This is the Sunday
Evangelical.
This is the former SDA.
>> Oh, that's new. The other day when I was
Was that on there the other day?
>> I'm always adding something new.
>> You're always adding.
>> Not only do we have a former SDA,
we have the offshoot SDA.
>> Oh, wow.
>> That's a lot.
>> That's a lot. So, when it comes to
things like uh lunar sabbaths
>> and feast days and feast days and things
of that nature. Now, I'm going to show
you. You can actually scroll down and
choose the subject that you want to
debate. You can choose whether you are a
beginner or you want to start at a
beginner level, intermediate or
advanced.
>> You can actually you can actually even
choose
>> the disposition of your critic. He could
be rude.
>> He could be angry. He could be
aggressive. He could be respectful.
>> It's good training, guys. the real
world.
>> Um, it's literally like you're in
school.
>> Yeah,
>> you're in school and you can practice.
So, you're practicing defending your
faith and that's how you get better at
doing those things. And
>> um
>> and they say when you really
you really learn something is when you
can teach it. So, you're basically
teaching it
>> Yeah.
>> to um whoever you choose.
>> Yep. And so if and and if you can do
that with
really if you think about it if you can
do it with an atheist well you would
come at if you could your knowledge is
your knowledge. You would come at it
differently with an atheist from a
different angle um and maybe even a well
with a Jehovah witness than a former SDA
and then an offshoot. you, your
knowledge is still your knowledge, but
you have to
>> know how to um
>> talk about it with them on where they're
coming from because their disagreement
with you is will be different than maybe
the atheist is going to be different
than the Jehovah Witness.
>> Yeah. And and a AJ AJ Lips, I see your
uh I see your suggestion and it's
coming.
>> Oh, yeah. That's a good one. Good one.
AJ I um I have a question like
does the like when you're like to be
able to defend mode you also have to
learn because you al I was going to say
you have to learn your enemy. They're
not your enemy by any means but to learn
>> what they think
>> exactly or what they believe.
>> Yeah.
>> I think that's important. Does the app
do that?
>> So what you'll see here is there is an
actually a um
let me zoom out again or zoom in. So
there's a Jeie's assist mode. If I
click, let's say I'm gonna click uh let
me click
>> the
uh Jehovah's Witness. I'm going to click
advance. I'm going to click um
respectful. And here is Jeie's mode,
right? And so I'm going to go ahead and
say um I want to I want to debate on
Jesus alone. Jehovah alone is God. And
then when I click begin spar
um what you'll see this is round one and
this is the J's assist mode right so
here's going to be their argument and
Jes is already an analyzing
right and he's going to reveal to you
where their logical fallacies
>> um how you should respond. So you can
either use the Jesus's mode
>> or you can say no I'm just going to do
it all on my own. Right? But if you're
like a beginner and or even if you're
not a beginner but you're like, "Oh, I'm
stuck on this, you can go to the Jesus
mode and Jesus going to is going to
encourage you." He's not going to give
you the the answer, but he's going to
say, "Here's how you can address this.
Think about this. Think about that,
etc."
>> Um, so again, let's do this because
there's a lot more to share.
>> There's so much, but we have we have
>> and I'm going to say this,
>> we have time for our guest, too.
>> Yeah, we do have time for our guest. So,
>> I'm a timekeeper watcher. This is just
the living mana space. Okay. If I hit
return to suite.
Now,
you see all of these tabs that I'm just
going to scroll across.
We definitely don't have time for any of
this.
>> No,
>> because these are all the different
>> I don't know if they can maybe read them
out because I don't know if it's zoomed
in enough for them. They I don't know if
they can read what you're going to try
to
>> just so you not to go through them, but
just to say what they are.
>> Okay. So, yeah, I'm just going to count
y'all.
What I'm going to do is uh here is a
palace and this is where all the floors
uh are. This is where
Sorry, you weren't even looking at the
comments, y'all. I'm sorry. This is
where um the rooms right of the palace
are. So when we talk about the photo
theology palace there are eight floors
in the palace and each room on these
floors represent different principles.
And so you can just walk through these
principles and basically learn the
floors, learn the principles. Let me
pull this up here.
>> I'm going to go to the photo theology
um image bible. Many of you will
remember this.
Remember when we were doing the 24
frames per second study? Um, so many of
you have seen it where you take one
picture, you take one chapter,
>> translate the chapter into a image and
then you'll remember for example Genesis
11.
>> If I remember the 11 as the two sides of
the tower, I'll always remember that
Genesis 11 is about the tower of Babel.
Okay? And so we created like a set of um
images that people could use to remember
each chapter. Here is the entire Bible
in these images.
>> See married to the creator, guys. And I
didn't even know this.
>> Yeah. Yeah. She didn't know this. So she
seen this for the first time.
>> I'm seeing this for the very first time.
>> So I can if I want to click study the
book of Exodus, study this book. And now
you begin to see here are the images,
right?
Right. If I flip the card, uh, Moses in
the burning bush.
>> Love it.
>> Okay. So,
>> and that's what I mean about everybody's
different learning um, preference or
like what helps. Yeah. Like everybody's
different. So, this this app is for
everyone. It is not a a cookie cutter.
>> Yes.
>> No. This is for the the visual learner.
If you learn, if you're um auditory
learner, it's it's for everyone.
>> Yes. And you will just see that I just
click this little globe button right
here. And here's what you see. English,
Spanish,
and it just goes on.
>> So, we actually have
>> I didn't know that either.
>> We actually have this in different
languages now.
>> I did not know that
>> the languages are still populating, but
as you can see, Spanish, right? And um
this is taking a little bit of time for
the language to pop for the languages to
populate, but here they are. And we
could add if you're like, "Pastor, we
need this in this language." Let me know
and we can add it in. Um okay. So, I'm
going to go back to English. I'm going
to show you one more thing. This is this
is right now maybe one of my most
favorite features on this on this
software. Um so, I'm going to give you
guys a demonstration. Okay. So, I'm
going to go to photo theology study
Bible. And then we're going to bring our
guest on.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. So, here's the photo theology
study Bible.
And in the study Bible, I'm going to
click the audio Bible commentary.
And
as you can see down here at the bottom,
and Gigi, I hope you're paying attention
because this was a suggestion of someone
last night after we did our little uh
onboarding session.
>> But uh here are five different
commentary modes. I'm going to choose
epic mode. Okay, I'm gonna choose epic
mode and I'm gonna choose Genesis
chapter.
Let me choose. Yeah, I'm gonna choose
Genesis chapter one.
>> Right before you click, I want to
respond to Veronica and she's saying,
"Please pray that her husband will take
time to do this uh do this together. I
have a tendency to want to do things on
my own." So, I just want to say um that
and I wanted to say this anyways, but
your Veronica's comment spurred it as
well. Um, like we do this as of late
together every morning
>> and it's a lot of fun and it's a good
way to start.
>> Yeah. We'll read the verses and she'll
be like, "What does this mean?" And I'll
say, "See that question button? See that
question mark right there on the text?
Hit that."
>> No, but not the question mark, but also
because you hadn't showed the other.
Okay. The question mark
is there, but I love the the light bulb.
the light bulb
>> because the light bulb in every text
takes you will just take you through the
history and the context like where it's
coming from like really the history like
I need more history stuff when it when
especially talking about the Old
Testament.
>> Um and it like
>> just the way my brain works I just have
questions about everything. Yeah. and
the light bulb thing is there and it's
like it answers the questions like for
the history and where just putting the
setting of this verse in context like
where this is coming from what's
happening it's almost like I'm not like
watching a movie
>> that's what I feel like it because
you're getting like oh so that's why
this is happening this is why they did
this and you know it just take it takes
the verse
>> deeper yeah
>> into understanding the context which is
so very important and how to apply.
Sorry,
I have to say on how to apply it. The
other thing is what the light bulb does
is it summarizes and it personalizes it
to how you how you can
>> um
>> well maybe I do that. Well, it does that
but then maybe I take it to the next
level myself. But it's like but it it
does make it personal. It does give a
summary like this history and how it
personally affects
>> Yeah.
>> or speaks to me.
>> Yeah. as a human.
>> So,
>> in this great controversy battle thing.
So,
>> there's so many things, guys. Like,
we're not we're trying, but we're not
even doing it justice. Go ahead.
>> Speaking of movies,
>> I'm going to click on I'll
>> let you talk now.
>> Yeah. I'm going to click on the epic.
So, let me just show you. These are
audio commentaries. Okay. These audio
commentaries, one is urban. I'm still
working on this one. One is ancient, one
is preacher, one is epic and one is
scholar. So basically these are five
different commentaries on the entire
Bible all based on the photo theology
principle. Okay, photoology principles.
So I'm going to click epic mode. And as
you can see when I click epic mode over
here, what to listen to?
>> Yes. To your question, Veronica, go
ahead.
>> Becomes epic. Epic Genesis one. And I'm
going to listen to Genesis 1. I'm gonna
go ahead and
>> Are you doing epic?
>> Yes. So, I'm gonna go ahead. They're
different modes. You can test it out
yourself, but I'm going to go ahead. See
this little music button right here? I
want to make sure that you guys can hear
first. So, let me know if you can hear
this.
>> Put a one in the chat if you can hear
it.
All right. Can you guys hear anything?
Put a one in the chat if you hear
music.
All right, I see no one.
>> Gota give it time.
Okay,
>> give me one second. Um,
>> no, they're not hearing that.
>> Let me try this and see if you guys can
hear that. And if you guys can't hear
it, it's okay. We will uh
Okay.
>> If if they can not going to hear they
can't hear hear, you can go on the app
yourself and um go to it's the listening
mode.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. And they and they can choose
>> how they you know there's five five
different choices for the commentary
like
>> if it's urban or
>> Yeah. Urban, ancient, preacher, epic,
scholar.
>> So you can choose but there it's it's
really good. My favorite is urban. His
is epic.
>> That's how different we are.
>> All right, let's bring our guests on.
>> Urban and epic.
>> Yeah, let's bring our guests on. We're
gonna see if I'm gonna see if I can get
this uh pulled up while I guest.
>> It is time to bring our guests. Our
guests have been waiting patiently. So,
we'd like to bring them on now. Welcome
guys. Everyone, hi Jacob again. Gigi in
the corner. Denise and Kashif. Um, all
right. Perfect. Thought we were having
Terry too.
>> Hello. I'm sure Terry can talk about it
during the segment if he wants to. Um,
but welcome. It's good to see all of you
and you are here to tell us about your
experience with the photo theology
suite. So, anyone can go.
>> All right. So, Denise, I'm calling on
you first.
>> Oh, did you say did you say me? I'm
sorry,
>> Jericho interrupted.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, Denise, go ahead. Tell us about
your experience with the photo theology
suite.
>> So, I actually love this suite. And I'm
going to take my glasses off because
just in case you see bags under these
eyes despite concealer, it's because of
this app.
It is addictive.
And it's really hard to sleep
with this app.
It has I I've barely touched the
surface. I have done the devotionals
which I have shared with family members
and friends and I love the devotional
and I've also I'm going to I'm going to
pick two things I love the most if
that's the case. Um, Sister Tante, can I
just pick the two things I love the most
about the app? Okay, great. So, the
devotional is fantastic.
This devotional,
what I love about it is that I can
choose a devotional that caters to me
where I'm at right now in a walk. If I'm
having an issue with work or with
another person or I just want to grow in
strength, this app allows me to custom
design my own devotional.
And
I tried the first time to kind of trick
the um AI like, okay, this is really AI,
so let me see what it can really do. Is
it really going to pull out Bible stuff
and is everything going to be correct?
It was it was really good. It was an
excellent devotional uh that I still
read. Uh to the point where I actually
had to ask pastor and he was so
gracious, can you create highlight
so I can highlight some of the stuff in
this devotional because that's how
amazing it was and still is. So,
whatever I'm going through in life,
whatever I'm dealing with, I can do
7-day, 40-day, I can send one to a
friend. Uh, I'm actually this
Mother's Day going to send
that to my mother. Uh, and what I'm
doing is I'm sharing devotionals in my
family space on WhatsApp.
>> I'm sharing devotionals with them.
The second thing I'll talk about which I
absolutely love is the Bible study. The
photo theology study Bible. I have my
second computer here so I'm looking at
it. This thing has caused me lack of
sleep.
I am an avid Bible listener and I have
used several apps in the past. I've used
Bible is I've used Bible commentary.
I've used all the Bible apps you could
imagine for audio Bible. And I love the
ones that have the drama and have the
music and have everything.
But the one thing I noticed was none of
them had commentary.
>> So I think Monday I got in and I was
listening to the Bible app and I like
this is really cool. I was listening to
I think the fall of creation part of it
and it was fantastic. Then
Pastor Myers decided he wanted to go
from regular 80 in TV screen Bible study
to IMAX Bible study and he created Epic.
So Epic, just so everyone knows, to me,
remember when James Earl Jones did the
Bible and we all went, "Whoa, you know
how the Bible with Darth Vader and James
Earl Jones?" Well, take James Earl
Jones, mix it with For My Nature people,
David Adabar, who goes, "The squirrels
coming out of its nest." Put those two
voices together and you have epic. and
listening to
and then you put the music background
cuz I'm going different levels. Let's
add music background. So in the
background you hear a soft amazing grace
in the background and you're sitting
there and it's like
I just blew my mind. I just blew my
mind. On top of that though, what I can
now do is I can custom it, ex download
it, export it and send it to somebody.
So those are the two things I wanted to
touch on. I don't want to get too
excited because I will just know that
just those two things, the devotional
and the study Bible alone will give you
these that makeup cannot fix things.
That's funny. Really quick, I heard you
share something. It was on Power
Wednesday this this past Wednesday. Um I
believe it was on Power Wednesday. I'm
sure it was. Um but you were just saying
like you were there was a time where you
you know you wanted to study the Bible
and you were into things, but you
weren't so into the Old Testament. Has
the app helped you with that?
>> So, you know what? You're absolutely
right. I growing up the way I did and
being I would be that Sunday evangelical
person that you press on that defense
mode for um the church app.
I was not into
Old Testament. I thought that was for
and pardon me for saying this but I
thought it was for the Jews. I didn't
think it had anything to do with me. Did
I like the story about Esther when you
know they showed the production story
one night with the king? I did. I
thought it was cool. you know, I liked
Proverbs, but you know, no, I I was I
was never a
Old Testament person, but I'm an avid
reader and I and I love history. And
someone actually I'm going to name the
person. I'm call them out. Brother Terry
said to me one said to me recently, "So,
you like reading half books?" And I
went, "Huh?"
He's like, "Well, you know, if you're
reading the Bible and you're not really
reading the Old Testament, you're
reading half a book." And I went, "Oh,
I'm going to start with the New
Testament. I mean, the Old Testament,
even though I know how boring Numbers
can be." So, I'm really looking forward
to see how Pastor pulls that off. And I
started with Genesis. And my goal was to
get through all of Genesis and go into
the next book.
I am still on Genesis. I'm on Genesis
chapter 5
>> because I keep having to relisten
and then I made the biggest mistake of
going I wonder what this would sound in
sound like in the other commentary. So I
picked another commentary and it was
like whoa. And then I wondered what it
would sound like in another commentary
because there's about five different
commentary and voices that you can just
stay in the book of Genesis chapter one.
>> So yes, this has absolutely
brought the Bible to life and I am
really
I'm really excited about
moving further along with it.
Amen. Amen. Praise God. Thank you,
Sister Denise. Thank you for sharing.
Brother Kashid, tell us what is your
favorite
things about the photo theology suite.
>> Oh, yeah. Actually, those um those two
that mention are my two favorite. Well,
um I did a devotion, a 40-day devotion
on fasting. And you wouldn't think that
um you could get much difference in in
the words that AI could probably produce
for 40 days, but um it really was
refreshing and we got something new
every single day,
>> you know. Um the Holy Spirit is moving.
He's working. He's doing things. And um
the devotion was was really really
helpful for me especially with um with
fasting. So it took you deeper into what
fasting is and and or tell me tell us
what where how it
>> how it led you through that topic
>> and you were experiencing it because you
were actually you were you doing a fast
you were you doing you were actually a
fast or you okay you were doing a fast
and you were
>> yeah I was doing some I was doing some
fasting I did a three-day fast um no
food at all um and then I did like
intermittent fasting for the remainder
And um you know the it's it's taken away
from from food altogether. You're not
even thinking about food. Fasting is is
no longer about not eating. It's about
what God truly wants you to do. He's
he's revealing his heart to you.
>> And
>> Isaiah 58 says it all. Right. Mhm.
>> You you you see how selfish you are
>> when you when you when you truly
understand what fasting is.
>> And for those 40 days, it was a it was
special. It really was special.
>> That's powerful.
>> Yeah. while using the study Bible. It
was um you know I was thinking I wonder
if if if pastor is gonna add this and
add that and add this and add that
>> and just see that other things would be
there and other things would be there. I
was like yes. So everything is here. So
I would I would be going crazy on
Facebook with my post like you guys need
to jump in on this. You guys need to see
everything is right here. No one has an
has an excuse with regards to not
knowing where to begin or or how to how
to start. Um, when you first get in the
app, it could be overwhelming because
there truly is a whole lot. You have to
really focus on one thing at a time.
Okay. Well, I want I want to see about
this. I want to see about that. And then
you could um you could take it piece by
piece because many times I've gone in
and I've been just jumping around and by
the end of two hours I felt like I've
done nothing because you know I didn't
focus on one thing.
>> Right.
>> Right. Right.
>> Yeah. Everything is there. Everything is
there. It's it's been
>> it truly makes you see
>> um
that the world is secondary. everything
that we have concerns for, everything
that we seem to care about,
>> it becomes secondary because you see how
much fun studying the word is. It just
it completely captivates you.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. No, thank you for sharing your
experience. Um, somebody used this in
the chat that I remember
>> when it first came. You're one of one of
the first ones to like get into the app
or that we shared it with, I think. Um,
and I remember your your response was
like this app that the learning
experience with this app is endless.
Like you were just like so like this
could just like and somebody said it's
next level. It's definitely
um you're not going to run out of of
learning experiences and things to do to
grow closer to God and go deeper into
the word. Um you're not it's not it's
not you can't stop going deeper is what
I'm trying to say with this app and
going deeper into the word and uh with
God. So thank you Kashie for sharing. Um
Sister Gigi, please tell us your
experience.
Um
so I was involved in some of the testing
early on and one of the things that
first struck me was uh Jebs the AI in
it. Um I want to talk about just a
couple things just two things that are
available to everybody not just the
members. So jeez, he is like having your
own pocket pastor and pocket pastor
Myers because um one of my one of the
things I did was I would I would
purposely answer questions wrong um to
see how he would respond um just to test
and what struck me was how kind he was
and how encouraging and how supportive
he was for an AI. Um, and so this this
suite is really appropriate for all
levels. Like if you if you had somebody
who was just learning the Bible or a
teenager or so forth, a young person,
the the the response that they get, the
support and encouragement they get, um,
even in playing games and things like
that, it it's literally like having a
pocket pastor Myers with you. um because
it it just re it just responds to you so
kindly. So encourage this with such
encouragement. Um one of my favorite
features of the main one, this is
available to everybody, not just LOC
members, is the analyze my thoughts
option.
Um you can have something you were
thinking about um or something maybe
you're like, man, I I want to go talk to
pastor Myers about this. I heard this or
I've been thinking about this and I I
really want to see what pastor think or
whatever. You can put that in the app.
I'm I'm sorry, in the suite and um give
it to Jez to analyze your thoughts and
he will he'll he'll go down that rabbit
hole with you. He will
expand with you. he will grow with you
and it is literally like just having
that conversation you know with pastor
to a point um because you get you just
get the encouragement you get that
knowledge
um library
uh that pastors built up over a lifetime
it's there and you get access to you get
access to it
>> you get access to his mind now
>> and I I recently there at this point in
my walk in my spiritual journey. I have
something that I disagree with pastor in
a tante on
um and um I'm saying at this point in my
walk, not to say it might not change
later. And I went in and asked Jesus to
analyze my thoughts on on my thoughts on
it, their thoughts on it. And I ended up
with bags under my eyes like Deny. We
all look we g Amra we need some
concealer because we all gonna end up
with some bags. I stayed up all night
and wrote a 20page paper only on based
on this analyze my thoughts with Jesus.
And then I couldn't wait to message
pastor and be like I used your own
software to argue against you and here
you go. Um so it really it it's really
helped. It's helped with my school work.
um it's a better resource than um I
actually have logos and it's a better
and easier to use resource. Um so I've
been working to try to find a way that I
can actually cite it in my papers. Um as
far as the um LOC
uh church part of it, my absolute two
favorite things are exploits.
exploits is I don't think we've talked
about it, but it is so cool. You guys,
you can go in there and you can say, um,
listen, I I really like uh I really like
playing mini golf. How could how could I
make that a ministry?
And it will help you create a plan.
>> You could be like, I I really like um
>> yeah, I really like anything. I really
like jewelry. I really like uh making
music, whatever. How or I have a
ministry idea, but I don't know how to
start it. It it helps you in all of
those things. It it it takes it from a
seed and grows and and will help you
grow it. Um and and also give you other
if you don't have the seed yet, it will
help you develop some ideas. I
absolutely love exploits. Can't say
enough about it. Um, and then of course
the defense,
uh, that I call it defense dojo.
And I especially love the coaching
feature of G's because it doesn't just
tell you like, hey, um, you know, you
could do this or you could do that. I
call it, uh, um, it it also helps you
think, like think and
critically evaluate the per the the
opponent. So before you've even gotten
into it, Jesus is there. Like, okay,
this person is this, this, and this. The
situation is this. It helps you to think
critically. And um it's really like if
you if you
in apologetics class, pastor talks a lot
about being in the ring. Um so it's
really like having having Mickey from
Rocky. If you guys watch Rocky, it's
like having Mickey in your corner um
telling you, you know, to the body, to
the body. um or telling you what the
next shot to be or or but in a kind lovy
way and how to how to defend your faith
and um you can also uh do it more
proactively like sister Atante was
alluding to where you can just ask Jes
to hey I'm going to go talk to this
group of people um and I really want to
understand
their faith a little bit what they
believe before I start talking to them.
You can ask Jes that. Um,
>> and he will educate you and give you a
PhD in whoever you're going to
evangelize to.
>> And um, you can also he he will evaluate
your responses to make sure that you
know, oh, you could have said that a
little bit better. Um, or maybe you're
go you've been in a discussion with
somebody and they put you on the spot
and you're not sure how to respond
lovingly or kindly or maybe they weren't
even loving and kind when they said it.
You can be like, "You know what? Let me
get back to you." Um, that's a really
interesting thought. Let me get back to
you. And then you can go take it back to
Jeeves
and be like, "Jes, help me to respond to
this." Um, how how would we answer this?
And he will help you can practice with
him.
>> Um, and get get your wording down and
get your foot get your footing down and
your wording down so that you're not
reacting. You're not you can respond and
not react.
>> Um, so those are my Go ahead.
>> Oh, go ahead. Okay, GG, I'm sorry I cut
you off there. Um, I was
>> No, those are just my those are my two
favorites.
>> Okay. No, that's awesome. I find that
defense part so important because so
many times
um we talk about our I know you and I
talk about this. So many times people
don't share their faith because they're
scared. They're scared. they don't know
like how are they going to come back you
know you know
with things that I feel like I can't you
know come back with or whatever um and
so they just stay silent because of fear
and this is an amazing you're learning
you're not just practicing you're
learning and the practice helps you to
learn like I was saying earlier like
they say that if you can teach something
you really know it so this is part of
that process
you're actually getting you're learning
and you're actually able to practice and
teaching it um against Jebs, which is
supposed to be any of those different uh
people from uh religions that have a
different perspective um from what you
do. And I think if that's I agree with
Gigi that's an amazing I mean there's so
many wonderful things but that right
there
>> is so huge because we're supposed to be
um spreading the gospel to the world and
um we if we're quiet we can't spread the
gospel and if we're not spreading the
gospel Jesus cannot come and we're just
going to stay in this world longer. So
this is to help all of us to be able to
share um with others in such an
effective way. I just had an idea. share
that with you later.
>> Thank you for that. Thank you for the
urban
>> Thank you for the urban uh epic that um
>> so just just real quick on that you guys
um I heard it for the first time last
night.
>> You're you're welcome. You're welcome. I
gave him that idea.
>> Yo, yeah. Thank you. Thank
>> It was both of you.
>> Okay. It was you and I, Gigi. I didn't
know you said something.
>> High five, sis. High five, sis. Okay.
>> She doesn't She doesn't like D's voice.
>> Well, well, no.
>> No, I don't. But
>> I do. What?
>> I mean, Denise,
>> I I I do in certain situations, but
yeah, I was just I just told him on
Thursday evening, we were actually
listening it. I'm coming back from a
date night and we were I was just saying
like everybody there's so many different
people that have so many you just want
to meet everybody. Some people that's
not going to fit and then some people
urban's not going to fit. So, we have a
variety. Try to meet as many needs as
possible. Go ahead.
>> So, and our and our ear our ear our ear
is trained.
>> Yeah. Our ear is trained to listen like
so a lot of time we have like we have
such a global church right and even
sometimes when I haven't when I haven't
spoke to sister Joanne or sister Ayana
in a while I can't understand them. Um,
and so like even to have somebody with a
Jamaican accent, um, one of the B, one
of the Bible apps I used to use, the
audio Bible app, they had different
accents that you could listen because
your ear your ear
>> just naturally goes to that. So, I'm
from the streets and I'm used to hearing
somebody talk very plainly. And even the
people that I would be sharing it to,
like Denise said, you can download this
and put some put a little beat to it or
a little if you're somebody who likes
more subtle music or whatever, you can
tailor this to who you're sending it to
that it would actually appeal to them.
Um, but just just for you guys who
haven't heard the epic yet, um, or that
or the the thing, picture picture
pastor's heaven's diary, if you guys
remember how listening to that just took
you to that place. Now, picture that for
every chapter of the Bible. And that's
all I'm gonna say.
So the urban the urban commentary it is
is designed for team
that's what you're listening to.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But it's it's you know it's team
it's actually geared toward the team. So
there are five different ways you can
actually listen to you can listen to
Genesis 1 commentary just the commentary
you can choose the Bible and commentary
so that it'll read a verse and then
comment and then a verse and then
comment
but in these five commentary modes
they're only commentary not Bible
meaning they're going to assume that you
already you already are familiar with
Genesis 1 and all it's going to do is
gonna give you commentary on Genesis on
>> context, depth, and you can listen to it
in the urban style, the ancient style,
the preacher style, the epic style, or
the scholar style. Meaning, they're all
going to come at Genesis from a
different angle, but still using the
photo theology principles. Let me say
this,
>> style come to you.
>> Caribbean style.
>> Caribbean island style. Pastor,
>> yes. Try to accent first, please.
>> The accent. Um, for those of you that
are asking, some of you are saying,
"Hey, I'm a member and I'm getting some
like, you know, errorstein when I try to
sign in." Just reach out to us and we'll
get it. If you are a member,
you will have access to this app, the
entire thing. Okay.
>> Pastor, do you want do you want to
mention the mighty network space to
report issues now or wait until um
Jacob?
>> You can mention the mighty network
space. Can you
>> Well, we should do it at the end, I
think.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> We want to get to Jacob and then we'll
end with that that information. Thank
you, D. So, Jacob, please share with us
what is your favorite parts of that or
what do you enjoy the most?
>> Yeah. So, uh right off the bat, the
thing I really like so far has been the
pre-built series. And so, um I started
off, uh listening to the prophecy pack
that combines Daniel and Revelation. Uh,
and so I I combined it with the Bible
reading as well as with the commentary.
And I was messing around with the
different voices through each verse and
and commentary just kind of, you know,
check out and see which I which one I
vibe best with. And so, uh, one thing it
did for me was, um,
it's also training me to learn how to be
remain focused because, you know, you
hear this kind of stuff, then something
will set you off, and then all of a
sudden you've been like thinking about
something different for like 10 minutes,
whatever, and realize you haven't heard
the last 10 minutes.
>> So, it's helping me to uh, really
maintain my focus regarding what I'm
listening to. And I'd say from a student
perspective, um, having started school
back up, uh,
2024 semester, um, and I've really come
to enjoy online learning because of the
just the way you can set yourself up.
And and so my my uh objective has been
to become an administrative
professional.
But, you know, with this online learning
suite, um, it I really see how it it
really is its own university, so to
speak.
>> So, and you're also able to to begin at
kindergarten level with with the picture
Bible and then be able to go through
systematically or on on your own journey
of learning. But but what I like about
that the most really having the
experience of sec sec secular school and
now considering a a true Christian
education is that I'm not having to
worry about the things that are being
taught. Um I'm not having to worry
about, you know, is there deception
involved? Is there something that's just
kind of, you know, swayed a certain way?
Whatever. That that I I I really believe
that it's it's spiritled and it's spirit
inspired and spirit taught.
So, um,
>> yes,
>> to me, it's like I'm able to I'm able
to,
uh, be be at the end of the day, it's
time for time for Bible study now, and
I'm just able to just hang out with
Jesus and the Holy Spirit and and have
the have the Holy Spirit teach me and
guide me with the assistance of of Jeves
or Reginald or whoever, but just be able
to understand that I'm I'm learning from
the master and and therefore all these
things that I'm learning, I'm I'm I'm
realizing that God is equipping me to
become a professional student, become a
professional brother, professional son,
professional neighbor, professional this
and that in a way that I'm going to be
able to use this information with
somebody at some point in a conversation
at the level that they need to hear it
at and that I can converse with them
about it in in a respectful and loving
way.
>> So, just trying to keep that in mind. Uh
when I first opened it up, I was of
course like the kid in in a brand new
luxury vehicle just pressing all the
buttons and uh putting my fingers on all
over the windshield and just you know
and it was funny because I wanted to see
okay, you know, what have I really
accomplished? So I went over to my
achieve I went over to my achievements
uh tab
>> and uh and this was before I I read the
little instructions. Don't do that.
Um because you can get lost in the abyss
if you don't have clear direction is the
I think what the quote was. But even in
in that little chaotic chaotic direction
uh style I was able to unlock six badges
and I even got 470 points. So you know I
accomplished something but
so what can I do with clear guidance and
direction? So that's why I think God's
uh God's u instruction for me and theme
for me this year is Jacob learned to
receive instruction.
>> So uh beautiful beautiful thing to be a
part of and and so much well of a time
investment when you got time to do it
with. So
>> yeah and and let me let me also mention
while you're talking about that you went
to the to the you know accomplishments
achievements.
>> I don't either.
>> Yeah. Um,
so I I want to mention there's there's
the achievements and what the
achievements is is it kind of shows you
what parts of the app you use.
There even there's even a game tab on
the app and the game tab where you're
actually learning how to play
um using Bible study.
>> Yeah. So,
um, there's a there's a photo theology
scrabble where everybody has like 10
cards
>> and the objective is once the text is
put on the table,
>> you're you're trying to be the first one
to make a connection between the text
and the principle that you have, you
know, that you've chosen in your card,
>> right?
>> You just keep going around. You're
actually building a Bible study together
with other people. Nobody knows where
the Bible study's going and Jesus is
checking all the answers. So you can't
just like say anything and be like,
"Okay,
so there's so
in the room."
>> So many different ways to to utilize the
app, but let me let me I know we're
we're coming up to the to the close of
our
>> side school here, but let me say this
again. I'm really encouraging
>> audience Can you guys not hear?
>> Okay. Yeah, there's data coming through.
I think
audio
>> maybe we should pause. So, um
>> um so the the mighty network the
>> I think we should pray.
>> Yeah. JJ, your audio is probably your
audience probably. So, you go ahead and
share.
>> Yeah. So guys, um, we put we put
together a a space on Mighty Networks.
It's called the LMC Bible Suite. And in
that space, we kept it very very simple.
There's three spaces. There's a fact
space where you will find directions and
the link to join. Um, you can, it's the
same link whether you're a member or not
member. It's just how the link responds.
Um, you'll find that there. You'll find
a a spot called sharing. That's where
you can go and you can put some really
cool stuff like, "Hey, I just did this
or I just did that." For example,
brother Jacob there. I did not know what
a preackaged service thing is, so that
sounds really cool. And you could post
that there and the rest of us could find
out. Let me go check that out. Um, but
the most important thing there is a
section called te tech help. And what
you're going to do there is make a post.
um you make a post there and you include
a screenshot of what you're getting,
what the error is and we will get back
to you hopefully very quickly but
definitely within 20 to 48 hours. Um
that is a place where you can put it and
we can all in one spot because right now
what's happening is some people are
emailing and texting me, some people are
emailing brother Gavin, some people are
emailing pastor texting them and it's
all over the place. So it's really hard
to do some troubleshooting. So, if you
can just go to Mighty Networks, it's the
LMLC Bible Suite Space and there it's
the tech help tab and you'll make a post
there and we will get back to you as
soon as possible. If we need to um make
a phone call or anything like that, we
will reach out to you. Um but it's the
best way to get it all in one spot so we
make sure to get everybody because
emails and texts can get missed. Um and
it's really it's really awesome and we
don't want you to miss out on anything.
Amen.
>> Oh jeez. Frozen.
>> I can't hear sister.
Shh.
Yeah. Can you guys hear me?
Oh,
yeah.
So, let me let me just say this uh
again. I don't know if you can hear me,
but I'm just going to talk. Uh
phototheologybible.com
photoologybible.com
um that is where you get the sweet you
can't hear. Okay.
>> Uh brother brother Kashif can can you
can you guys hear me now?
>> Yep.
>> Brother Kush you maybe want to pray us
out.
>> Yes sir. I'll pass you finish.
>> Thank you.
>> Go ahead.
>> Okay. All right.
>> Heavenly Father, I thank you for just
another um wonderful time spent in
Sabbath school. Lord, I thank you for
the way that you've given these gifts
and talents to our pastor that he can
produce this app, Lord, this suite.
So, Father, we just ask that um we know
that your Holy Spirit is involved and
he's guiding and he's teaching. So, we
ask that everyone who wants to do this,
who wants to try it out, that um that
you guide each each heart, each mind
into the exact um specific topics that
each person is trying to seek out. Lord,
Lord, I ask for clarity
for everyone as they study and they see
new things in your word. Lord, your word
truly is inexhaustible. And Lord, we
thank you for just blessing us and
showing us your love in so many
different ways. Bless our pastor, bless
our first lady, and bless everyone who
was watching and listening in name.
Amen.
>> Amen.
>> Amen. Amen. Can
>> I say one thing about the app
>> and the reload that you're going to see
reload on the bottom of the app because
pastor's always uploading it. And don't
let that freak you out. I mean, pastor's
always in the app. I don't know if that
man sleeps, right? But just go ahead and
click the reload button and the reload
button will reload a new version of the
app. I just wanted to get that out.
Thank you.
>> Sweet. Happy app.
>> Yes.
>> Bye you guys.
We're here in the wild plains of the
Masai Mara where we find an elaborate
ecosystem that draws thousands of people
each year. People from all over the
world flock to this place in the hopes
of gaining a glimpse of the biggest
animals on Earth in their natural
habitat. The mar is the home to the
blue-legged topi, the striped zebra, the
spotted giraffe, the bold and brazen
buffalo, the elusive leopard, the hungry
hippo, the nile crocodile, the laughing
hyena, the bombastic baboon, the
wilderbeast, the treecrushing elephant,
the chilling cheetah and the lazy lion.
Not to mention all kinds of beautiful
birds and creepy crawlers. The Mar is a
place that captures the imagination with
its rugged and wild beauty.
It is also the home of what many people
call one of the seven wonders of the
world, the great wilderbeast migration.
The great wilderbeast migration is known
as the World Cup of Wildlife. It is an
incredible, indescribable spectacle that
is only seen by a relative few who are
willing to safari deep into the plains
of this African wilderness. During the
cool season from October to July, over 2
million wilderbees migrate from southern
Tanzania here in northern Kenya. They're
following the rain showers that provide
water for new pasture. These hungry
mammals are in search for greener grass
on the other side of the Mara River. For
it to remain where they are is to die of
starvation. In order to live, they must
head north. They must come up higher in
order to survive. And as they migrate
upward, they are in reality passing from
death into life.
But the wilderbeast also seem to
understand that there are untold dangers
ahead of them. There are ravenous
predators on the prow searching for
their next meal. lions and hyenas in the
bush, leopards in the treetops, and
crocodiles in the river. And yet all
this danger does not deter them from
moving forward, upward, and onward in
search of new life.
And just like the great wilderbeast
migration that compels millions of
animals to move north, so too, God has
called the Great Advent
where God's throne is. For from that
throne in the sky falls showers of
lifegiving water to quench the dry
parched ground of our lives. The Lord is
calling each of us to cry unto him for
the latter rain of his spirit. And as we
do, here is the promise of God. The Lord
declares, "I will make them and the
places all around my hill a blessing.
And I will cause showers to come down in
their season, and there shall be showers
of blessing. Then the trees of the field
shall yield their fruit, and the earth
shall yield her increase, and they shall
be safe in the land, and they shall know
that I am the Lord. The Lord has
promised something better for us up
north if we have the courage to follow
him in faith. My friend, don't get stuck
in a spiritual rut. Don't rest content
with the dry, dead grass of religious
formalism or postmodern relativism.
Let us follow the chief shepherd as he
leads us to green pastures and beside
still waters. You see, like the
wilderbeast, in order to live, we must
come up higher in holiness and further
in faith. Now, God did not promise that
the journey of faith would be easy. For
the devil is walking about like a
roaring lion, seeking whom he may
devour. We may face bold attacks during
the day or spiritual ambushes in the
night, but we cannot allow the lion's
roar or the hyena's laughter to deter
us. For greater is he that is in you
than he that is in the world. And if God
is for us, who can be against us?
My friend, perhaps today God is calling
you to a higher purpose, a new
opportunity, a different calling, a more
fruitful field of labor. But maybe
you're afraid of failure. You're scared
of defeat, terrified by potential loss.
But if God is calling, do not stay back
in fear. For to remain still is to die.
To move forward is to live. So move
forward in faith. For though we walk
through the valley of the shadow of
death, we don't have to be afraid of
anything. For our God is with us. Trust
that if it's God's will, it's his bill.
And if it's in God's plan, he will give
you the promised land. Follow the reign
of his spirit to higher ground. Look to
the kingly shepherd who sits on his
throne in the sides of the north.
Receive the showers of blessing in your
life. And as you do, you will see that
truly the grass is greener on God's
side.
We hope you've been blessed and inspired
by this new Reflections of Hope episode.
This episode is one of many that's been
produced all over the world. If you
haven't done so yet, please give our
video a like, share it with your
friends, and please follow us on
Instagram, Facebook, and YouTube. If
you'd like to see more inspiring
episodes and get access to much more
uplifting content, please go now to
patreon.com/revelationof
hope and sign up to be a member of our
Patreon page. Your monthly support will
not only give you early access to many
more inspiring videos, but it will also
enable us to continue to produce more of
these cinematic object lessons from
nature. Our goal is to produce and
release these episodes much more
frequently. So please prayerfully
consider partnering with us so that we
may continue to share the hope of Jesus
all over the world. Thank you so much
for your support. Aloha and Marina
Welcome back living church family. Just
want to let you know that we are having
technical difficulties and we are having
to restart uh this uh we have to create
a new link. So, this link, what you're
watching right now, is about to uh be
cut after I'm uh after I'm done giving
you this announcement, and a new one is
being created as I'm speaking. So, stay
on the YouTube channel that you are on
and just look for the new link. It will
pop up and we will uh begin the divine
worship service there. So, all of you
don't go anywhere. We're still here. Uh
the divine worship service is starting
uh momentarily. The new link will be up
after this one ends. We look forward to
we look forward to continue to worship
with you today.